xinluhxlh.com 2019-07-26

# Privacy Policy

###  How can we protect your privacy? 

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy. 

###  Safe purchase at xinluhxlh 

We want you to feel completely secure when ordering from xinluhxlh. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet. 

###  Our Privacy Policy 

###  What personal information do we collect? 

As set forth in more detail below, xinluhxlh ("xinluhxlh” or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the xinluhxlh web site ("Site"). This information includes your first and last name, email address and a password when you create your xinluhxlh account. You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. 

xinluhxlh does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the xinluhxlh Terms of Use. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the xinluhxlh Terms of Use on their behalf. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the xinluhxlh Terms of Use, do not use this Site. 

###  Purchase Information 

When you make a purchase from xinluhxlh, we collect your name and payment method information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s). 

When you create an account at xinluhxlh, you can choose to save your billing information in "My Tang." You can also save one or more shipping addresses in your xinluhxlh Address Book. You may change or delete this saved information anytime, simply go to My Tang, log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. 

###  Services Account Information 

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the xinluhxlh services, including but not limited to, xinluhxlh's Transaction Platform. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at xinluhxlh. 

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to xinluhxlh. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to this Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties. 

We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on this Site and to track and measure performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties. 

###  Contacting xinluhxlh 

We will use your email address to respond to your questions, suggestions, and/or requests for assistance in using this Site. 

###  Other times we may collect personal information 

From time to time, xinluhxlh may conduct surveys and contests via this Site, email, other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties. 

###  How we use your personal information? 

Information we collect on xinluhxlh may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:  
Deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online  
Register you as a member of xinluhxlh  
Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchases  
Confirm your orders  
Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests  
Communicate great values and featured items to you  
Find and stock the products you want  
Customize your purchase experience 

###  When and with whom can we share your personal information? 

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives, service providers, and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; storing, sharing and retrieving customers' photo images in our Photo Center; enhancing and improving clients' purchase experience; enabling access to our partners' web sites; providing a personalized purchase experience; preventing fraud and completing payment method processing. 

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability) or to comply with valid legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) or as required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

###  How can you control the use of your personal information? 

You can modify or delete your personal information anytime, simply go to My Tang, log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. Do not share your xinluhxlh password with anyone. Other than on this Site, xinluhxlh will never ask you for your password. 

###  How can we protect the security of your personal information? 

Your personal information is protected by the password you created when you created an account at xinluhxlh (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. No Customer Service Associate or any other representative of xinluhxlh will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. You may change it anytime by going to My Tang. Log in with your email address and password, then click "Change Name, Email & Password" and enter a new password. 

###  More about your privacy 

We realize that making purchases at xinluhxlh, or any other web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our clients, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, email address or checking account information, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally. 

We believe that you have a right to know, before purchase at xinluhxlh or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it. 

We do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. You have the right to control your personal information as you see fit. 

If you have an account at xinluhxlh and you want to change, modify or delete any of your personal information, you can do so anytime by going to My Tang. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. 

xinluhxlh may provide links to certain third party web sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to activities conducted and personal information collected on this xinluhxlh web site. Other web sites may have their own policies regarding privacy and security. 

xinluhxlh will obtain your consent before allowing the download of any software from the xinluhxlh Site, and xinluhxlh will not automatically download any software to your computer system. Once you consent to the initial download of any software, you may receive automatic updates or patches pertaining to such software. You understand and agree that any material, including but not limited to downloaded software, required or automated updates, modifications, reinstallations, or software otherwise obtained through the use of the xinluhxlh web Site is done at your own discretion and risk and that you will be solely responsible for any damages to your computer system or loss of data that may result from any such material.
